There it is.
Huh?
Angel's Playbox Entrance
Angel's Playbox Entrance.
Recommended level: 50.
Recommended Level: 50
Same plan. Let's go.
Got it!
Was I useful, Mr. Elymas?
Yeah. Ruche, thanks for
teaming up with me.
Did you want these
Bear Shields that badly?
Shall we collect ten of them today?
No, you've gained enough levels.
The real work starts now.
What?
Level 20 reached.
Wow, you're right. When did that happen?
Our new goal is hunting Golden Raana.
G-Golden Raana?!
Loading
Begin Adventure
Episode 7\h\h\hGolden Raana Farming
Raana.
The frog monsters I defeated
after coming to this world
and beloved trash mob from Magic World.
Rampart Reflection!
Though there are many variants,
the Golden Raana is our current target.
Given our situation, I determined
we had to farm this dungeon next.
The shiny Golden Raana
has a low spawn rate,
but they have a high chance of dropping
an extremely valuable item.
What's more, their Attack and Magic
are low despite their high level,
and they lack offensive skills.
In other words,
they're weak in combat while offering
tons of EXP and valuable drops.
You couldn't ask for a juicier monster!
There are several bonus characters
like the Golden Raana.
Croak
In Magic World, they were affectionately
known as Golden Toads.
Croak
Many players said farming them was
the most fun they had in the game.
Golden Raana spawn frequently in
the middle levels of the Angel's Playbox.
And I know the best places to find
every monster that appears here.
I've heard of Golden Raana, too.
They say you can live off
a single Golden Raana for years.
That's what the adventurers
at the bar said.
Yeah? Then that makes things simple.
They also said this...
They're too quick to catch.
Even if you land a hit,
they don't seem to take any damage.
It's not uncommon for people
to chase them too far
and find themselves
surrounded by monsters.
There could even be adventurers
who died because of them!
Tremble
That's right. This world is similar
but different from the game.
Death is the end here.
People naturally tend to
choose builds for survival.
Farming Golden Raana must not be easy.
Golden Raana have exceptional
Speed and Defense.
Scratch
They're also totally immune to elemental
attacks, status effects, and debuffs.
Aren't we powerless
against something like that?
The Ironpiercer knife you gave me is
effective against high-Defense targets,
but I doubt it'll damage a Golden Raana.
I don't think I could even
catch up to one.
You're right.
Golden Raana boast a Speed of 67
and Defense of 200.
The Ironpiercer's 15% Defense penetration
is meaningless against its Golden Defense.
Attack: 67
Defense: 200
15% Defense Penetration
But...
Its Speed is more than double
Ruche's as a Pierrot.
And it's more than triple mine
as a slow Heavy Knight.
Defense: 200
Additionally, its Defense is 200.
Even a perfect Rampart Reflection
is completely negated by it.
Vital Slice also has
15% Defense penetration,
but that's not nearly enough
to deal damage.
Um...
Are we sure this isn't impossible?
Don't worry.
I've got a plan to farm them.
Even its seemingly
perfect defense has holes.
What?!
But do you have a skill
that can damage Golden Raana?
I've never heard of Heavy Knights
having skills like that.
I'm counting on you, Ruche.
Me?!
Anyway, you should have eight
skill points from leveling up just now.
Put all of them
into the Fool's Acrobatics.
The two skills you'll gain from that
are the key to our strategy.
Um, I'm glad you have
such high hopes for me,
but I don't have that kind of power.
Okay, Ruche. Let's run while we can.
Okay. I could probably finish it off,
but you're sure, right?
Monster: Toy Box
Yeah. That isn't our target,
and it'll start calling allies
once it feels cornered.
Do we really want to narrow
our focus to Golden Raana?
With your stability and knowledge,
if we defeat other monsters, I could
probably gain three more levels today.
It's fine. We're currently the perfect
level for farming Golden Raana.
Good. It's not chasing us.
Besides, I assumed
we wouldn't find one right away.
Really?
If we search all day,
we might find two.
Th-They're that rare?
But...
Golden Raana are worth
the time and effort.
Gulp.
But no matter how high your Luck is,
they're still hard to encounter.
Let me know if you start
to feel anxious or unhappy.
Don't worry.
I was only a little worried.
I'll follow you anywhere, Mr. Elymas.
Thanks, but you don't need to hold back.
Let's farm a hundred or even
a thousand Golden Raana!
I'll show you that I can do it!
I'm glad she's motivated,
but the market in Rondalm would
explode if we farmed that many.
Is that...
A Golden Raana?!
Don't worry.
I'll follow you anywhere, Mr. Elymas.
Is that...
A Golden Raana?!
We found one way sooner than I expected.
W-We found one. We found one.
What should we do?
Deep breaths, Ruche.
We need to stay calm
if we want to defeat it.
Got it.
exhale
inhale
You reached Fool's Acrobatics 10 with
the skill points from leveling up, right?
Yes. I acquired
the two skills you mentioned.
Good. Follow the plan.
Okay.
I'll wait here for the Golden Raana,
so herd it towards me.
Ruche?
Tense
It's okay, Ruche.
I can do it. I can do it. I can do it...
Um, it's okay if you mess up.
Tense
Deep breaths, deep breaths.
Here I go.
I've got this!
Golden Raana begin running when
an adventurer gets within four meters.
Croak
And the corridors in the Angel's
Playbox are four meters wide.
Even when a Golden Raana
is at the edge of a corridor,
you just barely can't get around them.
But that's only if you're
walking on the floor.
Acrobatic Amble!
You're not getting away!
Doppellusion!
Doppellusion
It's impossible to slip past those
illusions in corridors this wide.
And the cowardly Golden Raana
won't charge into it.
Their status effect immunity means
they can't be blinded or hallucinate,
but they can't see through
the illusions created by Doppellusion.
This is one of the holes
in their resistances.
Mr. Elymas, it's running your way!
Another is that Shadow Stomp
works on them.
It comes down to whether
or not I can land it.
The corridors are narrow,
but it's three times faster than me.
My shadow's only
50 centimeters long, but...
I can't screw up when this was my idea!
I bought these Magic Stones
when we got Ironpiercer.
Magic Stone [Holy Type]
Spend MP to fill with mana and release healing light
Their healing isn't very effective,
so they're rarely used for that.
But they can also be used like this!
Shadow Stomp
Shadow Stomp!
We've got you now, Golden Raana!
We did it, Mr. Elymas!
It's as good as dead now!
What? But how do you plan to kill it?
Flail
We'll have to score critical hits.
Critical hits?
Reading your opponent's movements
and landing the perfect hit
Critical.
deals 1.5 times normal damage and
ignores 50% of your target's Defense.
I see. And you've got all the time in
the world to try for critical hits, right?
You can do it, My. Elymas.
My critical hits don't do
enough damage to affect it.
What?
Didn't I say I was counting on you?
What?!
Scoring critical hits
requires skill and luck.
Miss. Miss.
Critical.
Flail
I can't go for critical hits right now
because I can't move.
But I've barely scored
any critical hits before.
It'd be impossible if you
attacked normally.
But you have your
original skill, Dice Thrust.
Dice Thrust?
Listen, you don't have
any decent attack skills.
You just soak up some hits.
That's the problem.
You're not actually useful.
You finally learned an attack skill, but
it's worth even less than a normal attack.
That's...
Skill: Dice Thrust. A thrusting skill.
Miss.
Dice Thrust [Common Skill]
A thrusting skill
Rolls a six-sided die and grants an
additional effect based on the rolled result
Rolls a six-sided die and grants a bonus
effect based on the rolled result.
Critical.
I guess that could work.
Exactly. On a six, you get...
A guaranteed critical!
A six multiplies your attack by 1.3
and guarantees a critical hit.
Total Multiplier x1.95
In total, that's 1.95 times damage.
Plus, Ironpiercer's 15% penetration
and a critical's 50% penetration stack.
Ironpiercer 15% penetration
Critical 50% Penetration
In other words, a six hits with
1.95 times Attack and 65% penetration.
Attack x1.95
Defense Penetration 65%
Flail
Will this really work, though?
Their use may be limited
or they may be late bloomers,
but there isn't a single
useless class or skill.
Don't let any individual's
assessment get to you.
You just seemed underwhelming
to Cline's party.
I'll say it again, Ruche.
I need you.
I hope you'll keep
lending me your strength.
I'll do it.
When you expect so much from me,
I can't let you down.
Otherwise, what would be the
point of being an adventurer?
Yeah! I'm counting on you, Ruche!
Dice Thrust!
Critical.
W-We actually did it.
Level 27 reached.
We did it! I'm level 27!
Level 30 reached.
Golden Raana are worth a lot of EXP,
but the best part is
the valuable item drops.
The drop rate is 50%.
Dazzling Raana Decorative Blade.
Dazzling Raana Decorative Blade
Attack: +12.
Market price: 17,000,000 gold.
Attack: +12
Market Price: 17,000,000G
A glittering Raana short sword
A hunk of high-purity Raana Gold
A glittering Raana short sword.
A hunk of high-purity Raana Gold.
We got a Dazzling Raana Decorative Blade!
Translator:
Sho Stifler
Timer:
Krzysztof Kunc
Editor:
Salem Alabanza
Quality Control:
Gabriella Alabanza
Final Quality Control:
Sriram Gurunathan
Both Ruche and I gained tons of levels
by killing the Golden Raana.
But it's not enough.
We don't have nearly enough
to buy that skillbook.
Grinding levels and gold is fun.
But this world isn't a game.
Next time, "Wandering."
Falling in this world
means dying for real.